> > Brian Holt: 我们现在正在使用其他工具。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We're gonna go
through some other tools right now.
我们要在这里安装的第一个将帮助我们
The first one that we're going to
install here is going to help us
保持较高的代码质量。
keep high code quality.
其中一个将是， >> Brian Holt: Prettier，好吗 ?
One of them is going to be,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Prettier, okay?
我想说的第一句话是 MPM 安装 -D，
So the first thing I'm gonna say down
here is I'm gonna say MPM install -D,
这意味着它是开发者的附属关系对吧
which is gonna mean it's
a developer dependencies, right?
所以当我把代码部署到生产
So when I'm deploying
my code to production
我不需要和它一起去
I don't need to have Prettier go with it.
这只是我在当地的环境
This is just for
me on my local environment, and
我要把这类的更漂亮
I'm gonna put prettier like that.
现在可以说 npm 安装，我也是一个懒惰的人，所以
Now you can say npm install like this,
again, I'm a lazy person, so
我喜欢无类型，所以我要把 npm - D ，就像这样。
I like to type less, so
I'm gonna put npm i -D, like that.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，现在看我的 package.json
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
now if you look back at my package.json
你会在这里看到我有魔鬼附体
you'll see here that I
have devDependencies and
它现在已经盯住了之前的 1.17 . > Brian Holt: Yours 可能
it has now pegged prettier 1.17
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yours might
如果你将来这么做就不一样了
be different if you're
doing this in the future,
但这是一个比较稳定的项目所以你可以去做
but it's a relatively stable project so
you can go ahead and do that.
现在我已经安装了 Prettier
So now I have Prettier installed, and
Prettier 将会做我能一直格式化我的项目的事情，对吧 ?
Prettier is going to do things where I can
format my project consistently, right?
我相信你们中的很多人都在研究一些档案
I'm sure many of you have worked on
projects where some files have tabs,
有些是有空间的，有些有拖尾的评论，
some of them have spaces,
some of them have trailing comments,
有些人是不会这样做的
some of them don't, so on and so forth.
所以， Prettier 是一个项目，只是把所有对话都花在了
So Prettier is a project that kind of just
takes all the conversation out of that and
对格式进行标准化。
just standardizes on a format.
我承认对某些人来说他们不想放弃他们的格式
Now, I recognize, for some people,
they don't wanna let go of their format,
因为这是最好的方法他们先想到了
because it's the best one, and
they thought of it first, and
我们都应该使用他们的格式因为他们比我们聪明多了对吧
we should all use their format because
they're much smarter than us, right?
我们都知道那个人，我们都不认识他们。
We all know that person,
and none of us like them.
所以最漂亮的是把整个谈话都带走
So what Prettier does is it takes away
the whole conversation, it's like,
不每个人都用同样的格式我们都被它困住了
no, everyone's gonna use the exact same
formatting, and we're all stuck with it.
这一切都和我们的选择略有不同
And it's all slightly different
than we would have chosen it, but
我们都是一样的
we're all on the same format.
> > Brian Holt: 这是我最喜欢的工具之一，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's actually
one of my favorite tools,
因为我真的不关心我的代码长什么样
because I actually really don't care what
my code looks like as long as it's well
格式化，对吗 ?
formatted, right?
只要有一个一致的格式，我就不管了。
As long as it has a format
that's consistent, I don't care.
最漂亮的是它是给你的
And the great thing about Prettier
is it just does it for you.
你可能注意到我一直在捣乱这些代码
So you've probably noticed that I've just
been messing around with all this code and
像这样做的地方就像超级恶心
doing stuff like this,
where it's like super gross, and
一切都在走错线之类的对吧
everything's on the wrong line,
and stuff like that, right?
读这种代码让你有点恶心不是吗
Reading this kind of code makes
you a little sick, doesn't it?
但是有了 Prettier，如果我这样做，它就会把我的一切都解决了，
But with Prettier, if I just do this,
it just fixes everything for me, and
我从没想过要这样做对吧
I'd never have to think about this, right?
我现在在我工作的每个公司都介绍过
I've now introduced it at every
company that I've worked at, and
我会继续为每一个我工作的公司工作。
I will continue doing it to every
company that I will work at.